(upbeat music)
- Hello everybody, it's our second almost annual
class reunion at Bletchley Park
and we have a wonderful group of people
and we'll just go around and do the standard thing
and let everyone say hi and say their name
or whatever they wanna say, okay?
So here we go.
- Hi. - Hi.
Hi, this is Özgür from London.
I took Dr. Chuck's pilot courses all the way to Capstone.
- Congratulations, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Hi, my name is Lotte.
I'm from Sweden and I've been doing Python for everybody.
- Did you come from Sweden?
- No, today I came from London, I live in London.
- Oh, okay, okay.
We had a person come from Paris last year.
- Okay. - Hi, I'm Steve.
I'm doing the Python course several times
and I'm one of your mentors.
- Right, so we sent Steven a sweet shirt.
Congratulations, you're a volunteer
and you've been working for me for how long?
- Couple years now.
- And you got a shirt.
- Uh-huh.
(laughing)
- Woo, and a nice trip out here.
- Oh yeah, of course.
So let's give a round of applause to Steven.
(applauding)
So, Steven is famous, yeah, sure, yeah.
So Steven is famous for telling everybody
to quit putting code in the forums.
(laughing)
- Yeah, he probably does that 20 times a day
to say quit putting code in the forums.
So, thanks.
Okay, continue on.
Hello, what's your name?
- Hi, I'm Caroline and I'm from London
and I've really enjoyed doing your courses, all of them.
I haven't done the capstone project yet,
but I'm hoping to go back and do that.
- But you took the history course.
- Yes, I did.
- Is this your first time at Leslie Park?
- It is, yes.
- Okay, so we got you to come to Leslie Park.
- Yes, and I've really enjoyed it.
- Cool, hi.
- Hi, I'm Lena, I'm from Ukraine.
It's my first steps in studying programming.
- Did you come from Ukraine?
- No, I live in London.
- Okay.
- And I want to thank you, Dr. Chuck,
for interesting lectures, for inspiration you give.
You're awesome, thank you.
- Oh, thank you, I really enjoy doing it.
It's really an honor.
I mean, the pleasure is all mine.
- Hi, my name is Dima, Ukrainian as well.
I'm here to support my beloved wife, Lena.
Originally, I'm just a software developer,
professional one, so.
- Ah, okay.
- Yeah, it's starting.
- You know Python already?
- Yeah.
- The people could find your course
and just advise me to study.
- I'm sure dinner's different now.
(laughing)
So you can talk Python at dinner.
- It's a bit colder, yeah, that's true.
(laughing)
Hi, I'm Brian from Richmond, Virginia,
here following your course,
and thought I'd check out the meal out.
- Are you on vacation?
- Yes, basically.
- When I went to Las Vegas,
I had officers with four people,
none of them were from Vegas.
Everyone is--
- Hi, I'm Jason from Wallingford in Oxfordshire.
I've done the internet history course.
- Great.
- And I'm now doing a chemistry course,
and I realize how much better your courses are.
(laughing)
- Oh, I might have to take that one out.
No, I won't take that out.
No, it's really fun.
It's really an honor to teach you all,
and to be in your homes,
and be on your phones, and all that stuff.
It just is an honor.
Hi.
- Hi, my name is Yu.
I'm a Japanese, and I live in London.
And I'm taking Python specialization now.
- Okay.
- And it's always fun, yeah.
- Hi.
- Hi, I'm Irena.
I'm from Poland, but I live in London.
And I graduated from linguistics, basically,
but I really fell in love in Python.
Thanks to you.
- So did you find out about the Polish connection
here at Bletchley Park?
- Yes, I actually watched the last year, yeah.
- You watched the video about the Polish folks?
- Yeah, yeah. - Cool.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Is anyone here for the second time?
From like a year and a half ago?
- Yeah.
- Oh, so you were here a year and a half ago?
- No, no, I came here three years ago.
- Oh, no, I'm talking about like the office hours.
- No, no, no.
- Okay, okay.
Hi.
- Hi, I'm Jeff.
I teach computer science, but I didn't study it.
So I had to study your courses,
and what you taught me about internet history three years ago
still forms the basis.
I still steal some of your slides from my lessons,
and I often get my students to sign up for your courses.
- Good.
I usually do, you know.
- But you, what level of school do you teach?
- Oh, I teach middle school, upper school,
what we call here GCSE and A level, so.
- Cool.
We gotta get more of that.
We just gotta get that right.
- Get them thinking the way computers work.
- Yep.
Mike, you wanna talk?
- I'm Mike.
I did the original version of the Python.
- The first one, the 10 week, the long one, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Well, cool.
Welcome.
- Yeah, they do very much.
- Yeah.
You're normal.
Hi.
- Hi, I'm Sarah.
I'm here from Oxford.
I took the original Python for everyone course a while ago
and programming finally clicked,
so now I teach kids to code at workshops and stuff.
- I don't know if you noticed,
but I use the word Sarah in a lot of my examples.
So now I have a Sarah that's the real person.
So there's Sally and Glenn and all these people,
but there's always Sarah for some reason,
but you're apparently the Sarah.
So welcome.
- Hi, I'm Robin.
I'm from Hemel Hempstead and I really enjoy your courses.
I love in Python.
- Well, welcome.
Welcome.
- Hi, I'm Karolina.
I'm originally from Poland, but living in London.
So I found one Polish friend here already, so it's nice.
I've been doing Python course currently on level three.
- Good.
- So I hope to make it to the capstone.
- Level three gets harder.
- Thank you so much.
Oh, yes.
It's getting harder, but exciting.
- Yep.
Good.
Hi.
- Hi, I'm Richard.
I'm doing programming for everyone.
I'm learning Python.
It's nice to learn something
other than hello world in our language.
Just doing it for interesting.
- Yeah, exactly.
Hi.
- Hi, I'm Claire from Devon.
I've only done the first Python course,
but it's really fun
and I think you're a really good lecturer.
- Well, thank you.
Thank you.
I'm part of the whole idea is to get you in.
- Yeah.
- And get you curious and so that your curiosity drives you
where you're gonna go rather than scaring you.
- I wanna do the rest if I can.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
- Hi, I'm Bim.
I'm from Essex, Thorac, Essex.
And I took the history of the internet.
- Okay.
Do you wanna talk?
- That's my son.
Just accompanied me today.
Thank you.
- Okay, that's it.
- Okay.
We're fine.
- Hi, I'm Anne.
I've just finished your Python
for everybody specialization.
It's fantastic.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
- You said that the capstone was a little too easy.
- Yeah, but it's the concepts behind it are good
and we'll be good to work out.
- See, I consider that a success.
- Yeah.
- If all the rest of the course made
the last part seem easy,
then ha, ha, I win.
- Fantastic.
(laughing)
- Hello, I'm Peter.
I'm on the second course of the Python,
learning to Python.
And it's very good.
I'm enjoying it.
So yeah, I like it.
- Well, cool.
The third one gets a little harder.
(laughing)
Hi, Matt.
- Hi there, I'm Matt.
I'm an archivist working for a museum in London
and I've reached a capstone
of the Python for Everyone course.
It's the most useful thing I've done in quite a few years.
I work a lot with museum collection data
and archive collection data.
And I'm now, after knowing nothing
about coding two months ago,
writing programs that can tear apart
my museum's entire catalog database
and do really useful things
that we've wanted to do for a long time
and do them in seconds.
So looking forward to building on what I've learned.
Thanks ever so much.
- You do know that I work at a place
that has a master's degree in archiving
that does technology, you know.
- I did not know that.
- You didn't know that?
- No.
- No, I work at a school of information.
- Ah.
- It does library science, archiving, nerdy stuff.
- Oh, I better get myself a US visa then, haven't I?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Better hurry.
- Yeah.
- Hi.
- Hi, my name's Pete.
So I work in the local government in IT
and I help out in a coded dojo at weekends.
But I don't like Python, so I need to do the course.
- Cool, welcome.
- Hi, my name's Luke.
I'm doing the third Python course
and I'm enjoying it very much.
- Great.
- Hi, my name is Roger.
I'm doing the history of the internet.
We are basically part.
So that's where everything starts.
From there to what we do with these ones now.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
Okay, well there we go.
That's our office hours.
We'll do a big scan of everybody
and let's have one more round of applause for Stephen
and how awesome Stephen is.
(audience applauding)